DAY 06 SYSTEM HEALTH & LOGS - 01/04/2026 14:45:35
--- SYSTEM FILE CHECKER ---
--- DISM CHECK HEALTH ---
--- DISM SCAN HEALTH ---
--- FINDINGS ---
SFC Result:
No integrity violations found / Corrupt files repaired

DISM Result:
Component store health: No corruption detected

Event Viewer:
Observed normal system warnings and informational logs.
No recurring critical system failures detected.

Conclusion:
System health is stable. Windows repair tools confirm OS integrity.
